<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://paravsalaniwal.github.io/firstrepo/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://paravsalaniwal.github.io/firstrepo/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-06-05T13:00:01-05:00</updated><id>https://paravsalaniwal.github.io/firstrepo/feed.xml</id><title type="html">📍</title><subtitle>Parav Salaniwal's fastpages</subtitle><entry><title type="html">N@TM Blog Tri 3</title><link href="https://paravsalaniwal.github.io/firstrepo/2023/06/06/N@TM_Tri3.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="N@TM Blog Tri 3" /><published>2023-06-06T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-06-06T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://paravsalaniwal.github.io/firstrepo/2023/06/06/N@TM_Tri3</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overall Experience: I believe this trimester was a great success and way to end my sophomore year for Computer Science. I felt like I accomplished and learned so much throughout the entire year starting from the basics of python and fastpages to creating my own online games. N@TM was a great way to show all the progress I had made and to cap it off as we presented our live tracking NBA stats analyzer, which gets all the stats of each player on each team and uses data tables, bar graphs, and pie graphs to help analyze the data and role that each player has on the team. I believe this N@TM was a good way to continue and end off the year’s solid projects, as last trimester my group had a really well developed game page. I think we impressed lots of people this trimester as we had a larger gathering around our project including students, parents, and even Mr. Mortensen. They all seemed very happy and proud of the project we had set up, because we were able to thoroughly explain the code behind the frontend and backend of it, and the functionality as well as how complex it was to even have data like this output. Along with the success I had, I was able to see everyone else’s success throughout the school in different classes such as 3D Animation, Photography, Ceramics, and a lot more. I saw lots of happiness and impressed faces as I walked around seeing people display their hard work. I was especially proud of the band performance that was played on the outside stage, as they played multiple songs so beautifully and well. I also was very pleased with the display in photography and all the crispy and clean photos that were taken as it really expresses people’s interest and things they love.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Python 2D Iteration and Animation</title><link href="https://paravsalaniwal.github.io/firstrepo/1.d/2.b/3.b/c3.1/2023/05/16/DS-arrays_lab.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Python 2D Iteration and Animation" /><published>2023-05-16T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-05-16T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://paravsalaniwal.github.io/firstrepo/1.d/2.b/3.b/c3.1/2023/05/16/DS-arrays_lab</id><author><name></name></author><category term="1.D" /><category term="2.B" /><category term="3.B" /><category term="C3.1" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several 2D arrays and Animations hacks are provided to further learn iteration and data in Python. The objective is to build a stronger foundation in iteration and data. Also, it is important to see concepts like printing color and moving objects in terminal, prior to moving to frontend development with JavaScript.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://paravsalaniwal.github.io/firstrepo/images/monkeys.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://paravsalaniwal.github.io/firstrepo/images/monkeys.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Sorting Algorithms</title><link href="https://paravsalaniwal.github.io/firstrepo/2023/05/15/DS-sorting.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sorting Algorithms" /><published>2023-05-15T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-05-15T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://paravsalaniwal.github.io/firstrepo/2023/05/15/DS-sorting</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working with Data Structures and manipulating data.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">MCQ 2020 Corrections</title><link href="https://paravsalaniwal.github.io/firstrepo/2023/05/01/MCQ2020Corrections.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="MCQ 2020 Corrections" /><published>2023-05-01T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-05-01T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://paravsalaniwal.github.io/firstrepo/2023/05/01/MCQ2020Corrections</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Total Score]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Developing with Frontend &amp;amp; Backend</title><link href="https://paravsalaniwal.github.io/firstrepo/quintinpartone" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Developing with Frontend &amp;amp; Backend" /><published>2023-04-28T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-04-28T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://paravsalaniwal.github.io/firstrepo/quintinpartone</id><author><name>Paaras Purohit, Chinmay Ramamurthy, Raunak Mondal, Tanay Patel, Qais Jamili</name></author><category term="student" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[To get started with development, you need tools. You'll learn how to get the necessary tools here using Conda scripts.]]></summary></entry></feed>